it's now time for our hashtag
Wars Ben Glee before YouTube I had
roughly the same number of YouTube
subscribers all right
points Anna uh before YouTube no one
knew what a flua borg was all right
points Ben before YouTube I got in a lot
of trouble for that video I made of that
kid drugged up coming home from the
dentist all right points fla before
YouTube I didn't hide my kids or my wife
all right points Anna before YouTube
people had to make their rape threats by
mail all right
points Chris from the producers of
friends enemies yes points R find sign
to catch and release a predator
points Rachel storage war crimes yes
points Tom non-consensual Sex in the
City
points Steve Lou THC K
points
uh blunter S Thompson points Doug Benson
Johnny cast points see Ariana
puffington Doug
Benson sativa AG oh boy points Tyler
this a two-parter bull mcale or Joel
xhale points very good very good double
angle there points I'm going to give you
double points for that D thank you Stony
Danza yeah points
Alice all the smeagle ladies so
good Adam my neck my back my and
my Kraken points very good Alice I can
see my sword when I'm with Orcs points
Mr Glazer moves like
[Laughter]
[Applause]
falor